

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### Contact

rakibuzzaman.contact@gmail.com +880 1705472922 Santhia, Pabna, Bangladesh

#### Links

My Website: https://mdrakib.co GitHub:

https://github.com/mohammedrakib944

Skills
HTML
css
Tailwind CSS
Javascript
React js
Next js
Ether js
Redux, Redux thunk, RTK query
UI/UX
Express js
MongoDB
Git
Problem solving skills
Language
Bangali
English

Hindi/Urdu

# **PROFILE**

I am a hardworking and experienced Front-end Developer. I have been doing development since 2017. I did jobs for a company called Sunno Software for 1 year as React Front end developer. Now doing a job on <u>Decentralized Brains</u> as Front end developer. Which is a web3 and blockchain startup.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Front End Developer at , Sunno software. Rajshahi, Bangladesh

November 2020 – December 2021

I am a hardworking and experienced Front-end Developer. I have been doing development since 2017. I did jobs for a company called Sunno Software for 1 year as React Front end developer. Now doing a job on Decentralized Brains as Front end developer. Which is a web3 and blockchain startup.

### Front End Developer at , Decentralized Brains, Rajshahi

December 2021 – Present

Blockchain and web3 technology are the future. Mainly for security purposes. That's why besides doing my first jobs I started to learn web3 technologies like Solidity, ether js, NFT etc. And join this start-up as a front-end Developer. Main tools Next js, React js, ether js (web3 technology).

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor in Computer Science Engineering (undergraduate)

January 2020 – Present

## **COURSES**

Redux Course, Learn With Sumit

August 2022 – October 2022

## **ACHIVEMENT**

Hackathon: BUET CSE Fest 2022 Category: Web3 and Blockchain

**Position: Second** 







# **PROJECTS**

I did around 70-80 projects in my lifetime. Some of my projects are given Below:

Decentralized Brains
Net Fee
My website
NFT marketplace
Instagram Clone
Movie Review
E-commerce
Dorac

There are lots more Projects

rakibuzzaman.contact@gmail.com